[Music]
the income benefit plan option offers
the dual advantage of life cover with
regular monthly income from the age of
60.
during the term of the policy the life
cover ensures your family can fulfill
their financial needs and achieve life
goals even if something were to happen
to you
once you turn 60 the plan starts
providing a guaranteed tax-free monthly
income till the end of the policy term
let's understand this with an example
35 year old shefali is a vice president
at an mnc who opts for a rupees 1 crore
life cover till the age of 75 and a
premium payment term until she retires
at age 60.
she chooses to receive 0.3 percent of
base life cover as monthly income
she finally makes regular premium
payments for the next 25 years which
provides her loved ones with all-round
protection against all uncertainties
as she turns 60 shefali starts receiving
a monthly income equivalent to 0.3
percent of pace life cover that is
rupees 30 000 per month that can be used
for her living expenses medical
treatment travel etc during old age
while shefali receives the monthly
income her life cover continues to
remain active only reducing to the
extent of income paid out giving shefali
financial freedom while leaving a legacy
for her family
a combination of life cover and regular
income through income benefit plan
option
[Music]